Contact

guilherme.barbosapereira@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ guibarbosadev (LinkedIn)

Top Skills ASP.NET MVC TDD

Fluttter

Certifications

JAVASCRIPT AVANÇADO II: ES6, ORIENTAÇÃO A OBJETOS E PADRÕES DE PROJETOS

JavaScript: Formação Básica JAVASCRIPT: PROGRAMANDO NA LINGUAGEM DA WEB

SASS E COMPASS: DESCOMPLICANDO O CSS

Scrum Foundations

Guilherme Barbosa

Frontend developer | React.js | React Native | Node.js | Javascript | Typescript | CSS

São Paulo, Brazil

Summary

End Developer

With 6 years of experience in the realm of web and mobile application development, I'm dedicated to crafting user-friendly digital experiences that make a difference. My journey through the ever-evolving tech landscape has equipped me with a strong foundation in front-end development, and I'm enthusiastic about applying my skills to create a positive impact on society.

What Drives Me:

My passion for software development goes beyond just coding. I'm on a mission to leverage technology for social good. Whether it's building accessible interfaces, contributing to open-source projects, or developing innovative solutions, I'm committed to creating a better, more inclusive digital world.

Beyond the Screen:

When I'm not immersed in code, you'll find me praticing some sport, like muy thai, running and volleyball. I also cherish quality time with my family, so barbecues on the weekend are a must.

Experience

Kyte

Senior Frontend Developer April 2021 - Present (3 years 4 months)

Brazil

Participe in the decision process about architecture and standards to be followed, help junior developer e deliver new features. Here the most relevant delivers were the tablet version of the app, and the brand new web version it.

Main technologies used

- React Native
- React Native Web

- React
- Storybook

XDS - Extended Development Solutions

Frontend Engineer

August 2020 - April 2021 (9 months)

São Paulo, São Paulo, Brasil

Part of the web development team and responsable for the decisions about architecture and patterns used on the web projects.

Main technologies used:

- React
- Jest
- Mobx
- Nodejs

Sorte Online

Frontend Engineer

May 2020 - August 2020 (4 months)

São Paulo, São Paulo

Maintenance and new features development.

Daily used technologies:

- React
- Javascript/jquery
- ASP.NET Core MVC

18digital

Frontend Engineer

June 2018 - April 2020 (1 year 11 months)

São Paulo e Região, Brasil

- Develop sites/hybrid apps(Ionic, React Native)
- Give my opinions about with techonology/pattern should be adapted on a project.
- Review pull requests

Technologies: Ionic 3/React/React Native

Education

UNINOVE

System Analysis, TI · (2020 - 2020)

Fatec Baixada Santista Rubens Lara

Tecnólogo em Análise e Desenvolvimento de Sistemas, Tecnologia da Informação · (2017 - 2020)

ETEC Dr Ruth Cardoso

Técnico em Informática, Tecnologia da Informação · (2015 - 2016)